我和我的哥哥们是历史上
最早的吸血鬼
REBEKAH: My brothers and I
are the first vampires in history.
是真祖家族
The Originals.
三百年前，我们把纽奥良当作家
Three hundred years ago,
we called New Orleans home.
现在一个女巫把我们引回这里
Now, we've returned,
drawn by a witch
她企图利用我哥哥克劳斯未出生的孩子
who seeks to use my brother
Klaus' unborn child
作为即将开始的战争中的筹码
as leverage in
a brewing war.
莎宾，告诉她们你看到了什么？
Sabine, tell them
what you saw.
这个幻象被如何解读了？
How was this
vision interpreted?
你的孩子将导致所有女巫死亡
Your baby would bring
death to all witches.
但是对权力的追求
REBEKAH;
But his quest for power
让兄弟反目
has turned brother
against brother,
使我们的家族更加分裂
Ieaving our family
more divided than ever.
现在以利亚回来了
Now that Elijah has returned,
我们家族能团结起来面对新的威胁吗？
can our family unite
to face this new threat?
（毒树）
你们就这样
度过我们第一次
So this is what you do
the first time we're back together
一家人重聚的时光吗？
吸血鬼读书俱乐部
as a family.
Vampire book club.
阅读陶冶心灵，妹妹
Reading edifies the mind, sister.
对吗，以利亚？
Isn't that right, Elijah?
是的，非常正确，尼克劳斯
Yes. That's quite right, Niklaus.
那这又是什么？
And what's this business?
这是求和礼物
This is a peace offering.
我想在棺材里
I presumed,
after so much time
干枯了那么久之后，我哥哥
desiccating in a coffin,
that my big brother
也许会有些饿了
might be a bit peckish.
所以我向我弟弟解释
So I explained
to my little brother
宽恕是无法被收买的
that forgiveness cannot be bought.
我真心想看到你行为上的改变
I'd simply prefer to see
a change in behavior
能够显示出你的悔悟和个人成长
that indicates contrition
and personal growth...
而不是这些没意义的
...not this nonsense.
我也不能白白浪费了她，不是吗？
Well, I couldn't very well
let her go to waste, could l?
我想我得去拿个垃圾桶
Well, I suppose
I'll fetch the rubbish bin
因为她弄脏了两百年历史的地毯
because she's staining
a 200-year-old carpet.
是啊
Oh, yes.
我对朋友感到愤怒
KLAUS:
"I was angry with my friend.
我说出了愤怒
I told my wrath,
怒气就消了
my wrath did end.
我对敌人感到愤怒
I was angry with my foe.
我没说
I told it not,
怒气越甚
my wrath did grow.
我日夜以泪水
And I water'd it in fears,
（凶手）
在恐惧中灌溉愤怒
night and morning
with my tears.
用微笑和温柔虚伪的诡计
And I sunned it with smiles,
照耀着愤怒
and with soft deceitful wiles.
愤怒日夜生长
And it grew both
day and night,
直到结出了一颗鲜亮的苹果
till it bore
an apple bright.
我的敌人见到它的光芒
And my foe beheld it shine,
他知道那属于我
and he knew that it was mine.
当夜慕遮掩了树身
And into my garden stole,
他溜进我的花园来偷苹果
when the night
had veiled the pole.
清晨我高兴地发现
In the morning glad I see
我的敌人横尸树下
my foe outstretch'd
beneath the tree.
早安
Good morning.
嘿
Hey.
听着，我知道我是这个家里
Listen.
I know I'm the only one in this house
唯一一个喝牛奶的人
that actually drinks milk,
but would it kill any of you
但是把它纳入
采购清单不会害死你们吧？
to make sure
it's on the grocery list?
说到采购，加上漂白剂吧
Speaking of, add bleach.
我真心希望我的弟弟妹妹
You know, I do hope
my siblings were
在我不在时有热情招待你
hospitable toward you
in my absence.
“在你不在时”，你要这么形容
In your absence,
as you like to call it,
也未免太客气了
which is a way-too-polite way
of saying
你弟弟把匕首插入了你的心脏
that your brother
put a dagger in your heart.
我被法语区的吸血鬼攻击
I have been attacked
by French Quarter vampires.
我不得不住到一个地下室
I've had to live in a house
with a secret dungeon
装满棺材的屋子
还差点被一群
full of coffins,
and I was nearly murdered by witches
深信我孩子是魔鬼的巫师杀死
who are convinced
that my baby is Lucifer.
牛奶
Milk.
他们一直对我不错
They've been fine.
你的弟弟妹妹奇怪地保护着我
Your sibllings are weirdly protective.
我知道我得谢谢你
I know I have you
to thank for that.
我很高兴看到你安然无恙
I'm just happy to see
that you're in one piece.
说到那些凶狠的巫师
So, back to the
murderous witches,
我有些担心
I have some concerns.
他们很邪恶，我的性命
They're evil, and my life
还是和苏菲德弗罗连结在一起
is still magically
linked to Sophie Deveraux,
这很令我担忧
which is not comforting.
是的，我想是时候
处理一下这个小问题了
Yes. I think it's time we took
care of that little problem.
我完全同意
REBEKAH: I'm all for it.
一旦她们解除了连结
我们就离开这个鬼地方
As soon as they're unlinked,
we get to leave this crap town.
我们得杀了谁？
Who do we have to kill?
也许谁都不用杀
Probably no one.
好吧，也可能是全得杀
All right.
Potentially everyone.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：毒树之果
我在那上面做菜，你知道的吧？
I cook on that, you know?
别对我发脾气
主演：约瑟夫摩根
Don't get cranky with me.
我是唯一还喜欢你的女巫
I'm the only witch who still likes you.
是啊，好像我不是在努力
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
Yeah. It's not like I'm trying to save
拯救女巫的遗产什么的
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
the witch heritage or anything.
她们会明白的
They'll come around.
她们只是太老派太害怕了
They're just
old-school and scared.
害怕什么？
主演：克莱儿荷特
Scared of what?
你对那个混合种孩子的预言吗？
主演：克莱儿荷特
Your prophecy
about the Hybrid baby?
爱格妮丝和她的畸形奴才们
主演：菲比托金
Agnes and her
freak show minions
在这方面可是很有实力
主演：菲比托金
had a real field day
with that one.
看到什么幻象不是我能决定的
Can't help what I see, Soph.
如果你是灵媒，我就是玛莎史都华了
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
Well, if you're psychic,
I'm Martha Stewart.
让开
Scooch.
搞什…
What the--
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
枯木上的毒苹果的诗
主演：莉雅派普斯
Poetry about poisoned apples
from dead trees.
看来某人很担心要做爸爸了
Looks like someone is worried
about impending daddyhood.
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
胡说，以利亚回来了
Nonsense.
Elijah is back.
有他在，所有的问题
都会变成精灵尘飘走
In his presence, all problems
turn to pixie dust and float away.
奇怪，我不记得最近被迫躺着的
Strange,
I don't recall any pixie dust
黑漆漆棺材里有什么精灵尘
from the darkness of the coffin
I was recently forced to endure.
你拿妈妈的咒语书干什么？
What are you doing with
mother's spell book?
为了换取我的自由
Well, in exchange
for my freedom,
我答应女巫黛维娜
I promised the witch, Davina,
我会把母亲的魔法书分享几页给她
that I would share a few pages
from mother's grimoire.
这能帮助她学会控制她的魔法
It'll help her learn
to control her magic.
我想我们可以从小小的解除连结咒开始
Thought we'd begin
with a little unlinking spell.
等等，你想利用她解除
Wait.
You want to use her to unlink
海莉和苏菲德弗罗的连结？
Hayley from Sophie Deveraux?
苏菲假借名义把我们骗回这里
Sophie brought us to this town
under false pretenses.
她并不是只想让我们
扳倒马塞尔和他手下
She doesn't just want us to take
down Marcel and his minions.
她想要回黛维娜
制片：兰斯安德森
She wants to take
Davina back.
所以她利用魔法、威胁
和半真半假的话
So she yoked
her own cause to ours
将她的目的和我们的目的结合
with magic, threats,
and half-truths.
一切到此为止
Well, no more.
此刻，我们和苏菲德弗罗的交易
As of now, our deal
with Sophie Deveraux
无效
is null and void.
尼克劳斯，我需要你跟我来
Niklaus, I need you
to come with me.
我需要单独和黛维娜在一起五分钟
I need five minutes
alone with Davina.
你得确保我不会被打断
You need to make certain
that I am not interrupted.
你留在这里照顾海莉
You stay here and watch Hayley.
我怎么成超级保母了？
How did I get
elected Supernanny?
更重要的是，是谁让他主事的？
More importantly,
who put him in charge?
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
一切都还好吧？
Hey, is everything okay?
需要帮你拿点什么吗？
Can I get you something?
我知道你想要一枚日光戒指，孩子
Look. I know you want
a daylight ring, kid.
给你个提示
我手下有比你早80年的还等着呢
Little heads-up,
I got guys 80 years ahead of you.
知道了
抱歉
Noted. Sorry.
等一下
Wait.
编剧：查理察尔邦尼
黛安艾德穆强
你认识克劳斯米卡森
You know Klaus Mikaelson.
有几次我要你送他回去
I asked you to give him
a lift home a couple times
皇宫饭店
导演：麦克艾罗维兹
对吧？
to the Palace Royale Hotel, right?
嗯，对，皇宫饭店
Um, yeah, the Palace Royale.
我去了他的饭店
You see, I stopped by his hotel
to say sorry
想要为我们的争执道歉
about an argument we had.
结果他说谎，他不住在那里
Turns out, he lied
about living there.
说谎了
Lied.
你有没有听过一句话
Did you ever hear the phrase
“为王者难安”?
uneasy is the head
that wears the crown?
“魔戒”吗？
Uh, Lord of the Rings?
不，莎士比亚说的
No. Shakespeare.
在我还是小孩的时候
克劳斯教会我欣赏
When I was a kid,
Klaus taught me how to read
那些戏剧，讲的都是一个国王
with those plays,
always about some king
赢得了天下却失去了灵魂
who gained the world
but lost his soul,
但现在我懂了
but now I get it.
当一切尘埃落定
See, when it's all said and done
看看身边自己建立的帝国
and you look around
at the empire you built,
唯一重要的是你可以信任谁
the only thing that matters
is who you can trust.
一定有你
There's got to be somebody somewhere
能信任的人
that you can trust.
愿意与你同甘共苦
To stick to you
through thick and thin.
坚持到最后的人
To the bitter end.
山姆对佛罗多说的
Sam to Frodo,
“魔戒现身”
Fellowship of the Ring.
确实有
Yeah, there is someone.
我们曾经是最好的朋友
We used to be best friends.
我答应过你的
I made you a promise.
进来吧
Come in.
宽恕我的罪行，神父
Bless me, father,
for I have sinned.
已经有…一年了
It's been, oh, a year
我都没有好好和你聊过
since I've had
a good conversation with you.
卡蜜儿
Camille.
你一直躲着我，基叔叔
You've been avoiding me, Uncle K.
躲着我最爱的侄女？绝对不会
My favorite niece?
Never.
别说谎，这可是教堂
Don't lie.
This is a church.
再说，我是来寻求专业建议的
Besides, I came about
professional advice.
是有关西恩的
About Sean.
解结咒？
The Spell of Unknotting?
这是一个血结
This is a sanguinem knot.
女巫将其看作代表性的魔法
The witches use it
as representational magic.
如果你能用这个咒语解开这团绳子
If you can unknot this
rope using that spell,
你就向控制魔法
you'll have taken
迈了一大步
an important step towards control.
这是我母亲后期的咒语之一
This is one of my
mother's later spells.
需要的力量远超出你的想像
Requires much more power
than you realize.
如果你能完成这个
If you can perform this,
我会再带一页来
I shall return with another page.
下一次就是你选的咒语了
A spell of your
choosing next time.
因为我是个受虐狂
Apparently,
because I'm a masochist,
今天我去了西恩的坟墓…
I went by Sean's grave today, and--
该死
我本想在你看见前清理干净的
Damn it.
I was hoping to get that
cleaned up before you saw it.
希望没有让你太难过
I hope it didn't
upset you too much.
一点都没有让我烦心
It didn't bother me at all.
这就是问题，我就是为这来的
That's the problem.
That's why I'm here.
这周来我每晚都睡得很香
I've slept like a baby
every night this week,
即使是我的双胞胎哥哥就在
even though
my twin brother hacked
离这告解室不到两英尺的地方
nine priests to death
砍死了九名牧师
not two feet from this confessional.
我最近约会的那个人，马赛尔
A guy I've been seeing, Marcel,
也不怎么理我了
has been blowing me off.
管他呢，我只不过和他约过两次会
Whatever. I've gone on
two dates with the guy,
比起看到我哥哥坟墓上
and I'm more upset about that
被人涂写着“凶手”
than seeing "murderer"
我更为此感到失落
scrawled across my brother's grave.
这就叫做治愈，卡蜜
It's called healing, Cami.
大屠杀后的几个月
For months after the massacre,
我满脑子都是这件事
I couldn't think of anything else,
然后突然间，都消失了
and then suddenly, nothing.
我需要感觉到痛苦
I need to feel that pain.
没有那痛苦，我感觉破碎，空虚
Without it,
I feel broken, empty,
就像是该怪谁
Iike there's someone to blame
而我却让他们逃脱了
and I'm letting them
get away with it.
听着，如果你找到了
Listen.
If you have found a way
忘记的办法
不要质疑它
to turn it off,
don't question it.
唯一需要对西恩行为负责的
The only person
that is responsible
就是他自己
for Sean's behavior is Sean.
你真的这么认为吗？
Do you really believe that?
是的
Yes.
我是这么认为
I do.
放开我
Let go of me.
放开她
Leave her be.
杀了我来抓住克劳斯或是他的孩子
Killing me to get
to Klaus or his baby
不是解决办法
is not the answer.
我不会杀了你的，苏菲
I'm not gonna kill you, Sophie.
你出生的那天我也在场
I was there
the day you were born.
我是我们女巫族群最后的长老
I'm the last remaining elder
of our coven.
保护我们的力量是我的职责
It is my duty
to protect our power,
如果有天那个孩子出生
我们的力量就不算什么了
and our power means nothing
if that baby grows another day.
莎宾的预兆很明显了
Sabine's omen was clear.
那个孩子会让我们都死去
That baby will bring
death to us all.
你打算怎么做？
What are you gonna do?
天啊，不
不，爱格妮丝，不要
Oh, God, no.
No. Agnes, no.
不，不要，不要…
No. No!
Don't do this--
怎么了？
What the hell was that?
我哪知道
Hell if I know.
我感觉被刺了一下
It felt like I was being stabbed.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
是爱格妮丝
It was Agnes.
她的人带走了苏菲
Her men took Sophie.
你主事的第一天，哥哥
Day one with you in charge, brother,
那个和海莉连结的女巫
and already the witch link
to Hayley
已经被狂热份子劫走了
has been abducted by zealots.
她在哪？
Where is she?
如果我告诉你们爱格妮丝在哪
你们会杀了她的
If I tell you where Agnes is,
you'll just kill her.
有那么明显吗？
Is it that obvious?
听着，我知道她有点疯在
Look.
I know she's a little cuckoo...
但她是我们最后一个在世的长老了
...but she's our last living elder.
这也许对你们来说没什么
That might not mean
a lot to you,
但对我们来说却很重要
but it means plenty to us.
只有长老才能施重要的咒语
The elders are the only ones
who can do important spells.
比如完成收获祭仪式
Like completing the Harvest ritual.
你知道那事？
You know about that?
我知道的事情会让你瞠目结舌的
Oh, you'd be astounded
by the things I know.
请允许我按事情的重要性
Allow me to entertain you
一一为你说明
with today's list of priorities.
第一解除你朋友苏菲的连结
One, unlink your friend Sophie
这样她就再也不能控制
so she no longer controls the fate
怀着我孩子那女人的命运了
of the woman carrying my child.
第二、说服我哥哥接受
Two, convince
my brother to accept
我为最近冒险的行为
my heartfelt apologies
真心的道歉
for some recently dodgy behavior.
第三…没有第三
Three, there is no three.
我相信我弟弟想表达的是
I believe what my brother is
attempting to communicate here
你们长老的性命
is that neither the life
of this elder,
收获祭仪式以及你们女巫
nor the Harvest ritual,
nor your coven's connection to magic
与魔法的联系
都与他无关
are of any relevance to him whatsoever.
说吧
Now talk.
提艾里
Thierry.
马赛尔
Marcel.
又来惩罚我吗？
Come to punish me again?
有人问我，有没有
Someone asked
if there's anyone
我一直信任的人
I ever trusted.
我只想到了一个名字
I only came up with one name.
就是你
You.
所以，提艾里
我们俩需要聊一下
So, Thierry, you and l
are gonna have a little talk.
是有关克劳斯米卡森
About Klaus Mikaelson.
恶魔宝宝吃点心的时间到了
REBEKAH: It's time for
the demon spawn to snack.
我真心希望你别这样叫她
I really wish you
wouldn't call her that.
抱歉，你想好别的名字了吗？
I'm sorry.
Have you picked another name yet?
拿一个
种植园里多的是
Take one. The plantation
is lousy with them.
脖子怎么样了？
How's your neck?
感觉没事，好奇怪
I feel fine,
which is weird.
我确定这和苏菲有关
I'm sure this is Sophie-related.
帮我个忙，别在我的看顾下死了
Well, do me a favor
and don't die on my watch.
不然我耳根就别想清净了
I'll never hear the end of it.
我第一次见到你的时候
You know, when l
first met you,
我觉得你真是个贱人
I thought you
were a real bitch.
是什么让你改变了想法？
What changed your mind?
我还是觉得你是个贱人
Oh, I still think
you're a bitch.
只是我开始喜欢你这点了
I've just grown
to like that about you.
你这么说真好啊
Well, that's sweet
of you to say.
我走后你也要记着
Remember it when I'm gone.
走？你要去哪？
Gone?
Where are you going?
我来这里只是为了确保
I only came to town to make sure
以利亚一切都好
everything was okay with Elijah.
他没事，他还没有惩罚克劳斯
He's fine,
and he hasn't punished Klaus
用匕首封住他
所以，一如既往
for daggering him,
so, as usual,
他们会非常亲密的
they'll be thick as thieves,
而我会被留下来收拾烂摊子
and I'll be left
to clean up the mess.
是时候我该开溜了
It's time for me to fly the coop.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我不知道
I don't know.
大概是害喜吧
Probably morning sickness.
事实上你发烧了
Oh, you're burning up, actually.
爱格妮丝用一根针刺了我
(GROANS)
Agnes stuck me with a needle.
这东西很久以前被下了咒
(CONTlNUES GRUNTlNG)
Cursed objects
were created a long time ago.
我们利用它们，这样我们使用魔法
We use them so we don't get busted
就不会被马赛尔发现
by Marcel for doing magic.
她用的那个叫做哀伤之针
The one she used is called
the Needle of Sorrows.
是在1860年被下咒…
It was cursed in 1860, when--
跳过那些陈年琐事
告诉我们它有什么作用，亲爱的
Jump ahead a few decades
and tell us what it does, love.
它只有一个作用
It has one purpose.
升高她的血液温度以杀掉她肚里的孩子
To kill a child in utero
by raising her blood temperature.
为了让她流产
It's for a miscarriage.
我们还有多少挽救的时间？
So how much time do
we have to fix this?
今晚涨潮时这个东西
就会发挥它应有的作用
It'll do what it's meant to
by tonight's high tide.
相信我，这绝对有效
And, believe me,
It will work.
我曾见她在一个小孩身上用过
类似的东西让他发疯
I saw her use a similar object
on a kid who went mad
并杀掉了一群牧师
and killed a bunch of priests.
我想和这个爱格妮丝聊聊
I'd like to have a little chat
with this Agnes.
在哪能找到她？
Where can I find her?
你找不到的
You won't.
她有无数的藏身之处来等待事情结束
There are a thousand places
she could hole up to wait it out.
这正是我们为什么要解除
你与海莉的连结
That's precisely why we need
to unlink you from Hayley,
不能再让她或孩子受到伤害
no more danger
towards her or the child.
不，什么？
No. What?
如果我失去了跟海莉的连结
If I am not linked to Hayley,
我就没有任何筹码了
I lose my leverage on you.
我们做了交易的
We had a deal.
我们可不是同一阵营的，苏菲德弗罗
We are not on the same side,
Sophie Deveraux.
我们的交易不再有效了
Our deal no longer stands.
这意味着你要赦免我吗？
Does this mean
you're pardoning me?
你知道我不能那样做
Aw, you know I can't do that.
你违反了我最重要的规矩
You broke my number-one rule.
你杀了一个吸血鬼，小提
You killed a vampire, T.
如果就这么算了，会显得我很软弱
I let that go,
it'll make me look weak.
我早就警告你小心克劳斯了
I warned you about Klaus.
是啊，我该听你的
Yeah.
I should've listened.
这家伙来到我的地盘几个月了
This guy has been
in my town for months
却不让人知道他落脚的地方
but hiding where
he lays his head at night.
我想知道他还隐瞒了些什么
What else is he hiding
is what I want to know.
之前我没有听你的
I didn't listen to you before,
但我现在一定会相信你
but I sure as hell am now.
告诉我那晚到底发生了什么事
Tell me about the night
that got you put in here,
狂欢节的时候说不定你就能出去了
and you might find yourself
out by Mardi Gras.
化装舞会那天晚上
The night of the
masquerade party,
你派我们去女巫那
you sent us rousting
in the Cauldron
骚扰她们
to mess with the witches.
当麦克斯过去时
So when Max came in rousting,
他直接咬了凯蒂的喉咙
he went right for Katie's throat.
你只是说骚扰，没说杀人
Now, you said to roust.
You didn't say to kill.
他是夜行者，而我是日行者
Now, he's a Nightwalker.
I'm a Daywalker.
我叫他住手，但他不听
I told him to stop,
and he wouldn't.
所以我制止了他
So, I stopped him.
那晚的事不断在我脑海中浮现
That night is on an
endless loop in my head.
我想麦克斯可能被魅惑了
I think Max was compelled.
不可能，我的手下体内都有马鞭草
No.
All my guys are on vervain.
如果克劳斯放了他们的血就没有了
Not if Klaus drained them.
麦克斯在骚扰行动前
Max went missing
for a couple of days
失踪了好几天，不是吗？
before the rousting, right?
小提，他们在你女友的店里
T, they found stuff you and your girl
搜到了你们从我这偷走的东西
stole from me in her shop.
你去过灰色花园吗？
Have you ever been
to the Jardin Gris?
那里的商品眼花缭乱的
You can't find your own hand
你根本不可能轻易发现什么
in front of you face in there,
尽管如此，有人进去
and yet somehow
someone went in there,
只过了短短几分钟
and after a couple of minutes,
就找到了失窃的物品？
they found some stolen goods?
不信你自己去那看看
Go there, see for yourself...
但我告诉你，除了麦克斯
...but I'm telling you,
besides Max,
你的人里一定还有别人
somebody else in the crew
被魅惑了
had to be compelled.
小心自己人
Watch your back.
几个游客失踪，没问题
So a few tourists go missing, okay.
我们能掩饰过去，不是难事
We can spin it, no problem,
但你知道对市议会讲什么
but do you know
how hard it is to sell
瓦斯泄漏有多牵强吗
a gas-leak story
to the city council
尤其当教堂一大片窗户这样
when a bunch
of church windows
神秘地爆炸？
magically explode?
别这样，市长先生
Come on, Mr. Mayor.
你当这是竞选办论吗？
What is this,
an electoral debate?
马赛尔越权了，我会对付他
Marcel overstepped.
I will handle it.
说得倒轻松
Easier said than done.
马赛尔可不是那么好对付的
Marcel is quite
the little warrior. Ah-ah.
你是哪位？
Who the hell are you?
我叫克劳斯
My name is Klaus,
你们就是那群
and you lot are the Faction.
维系着城市超自然生物平衡的
Pillars of the community
who maintain
社区中的栋梁者吧
the city's supernatural balance.
我该知道的
Well, I should know.
我创立了这个组织，只不过在我那时
I created this group.
Only in my day,
全是一帮海盗和腐败的政客
it was a bunch of pirates
and corrupt politicians.
看起来一点都没变啊
Looks like nothing's changed.
有一件事变了
One thing has.
现在只接受人类
It's exclusively human now.
吸血鬼不准加入，尤其是真祖
No vampires allowed,
especially no Originals.
我不是要来加入的
(MOCKlNG LAUGH)
I haven't come to join.
我是来请你们动用
I've come to ask this group
你们丰富的资源
to utilize it's considerable resources
去找一个叫爱格妮丝的女巫长老
to find a witch elder named Agnes.
我只需要一个地址
All I need is an address.
为什么我们要帮你？
And why would we want to help you?
如果我告诉你爱格妮丝
What if I told you that Agnes
能解开
was the answer to a question
自你逃离这个城市后
you've been asking since
you ran screaming
一直想解答的疑问
from this town?
她就是对你侄子西恩
That she is the witch
下咒的女巫呢？
who hexed your nephew, Sean?
我们需要点时间讨论…
We'd need some time to discuss--
我没有时间
I don't have time!
我也不喜欢别人叫我等待
Nor do I like being asked to wait.
或许你可以吓唬住
You may have all the vampires
这个城市所有的吸血鬼
in this town
cowering in fear,
但现在你是在跟人类打交道
but right now,
you are dealing with the humans,
除非你打算杀掉我们所有人
and unless you plan on
killing all of us,
不然我建议你照我的话做
I politely suggest you do
as I say,
给我们时间讨论一下
and give us time to discuss it.
你知道我欣赏你什么吗，神父？
You know,
what I like about you, Father,
就是你明知道我的名声
is, you're aware of my reputation
却仍然无惧与我作对
and yet still
you stand tall against me.
我很敬佩
It's admirable.
你有一小时
You have one hour.
找到那个女巫
Track down that witch.
通话记录什么的，九区有我们的人
Cell phone records,
our guys in the Ninth.
为了那个吸血鬼吗？
For the vampire?
不，是为了我
No, for me.
不要烦躁，好吗？
以利亚马上就回来
Stop fussing, will you?
Elijah will be here any minute.
我觉得好像被放进了微波炉一样
I feel like
I've been microwaved.
就算你怀着孩子
Hey, just because
you're carrying a baby
也不代表你就能像个孩子一样任性
doesn't mean you get
to act like one.
我想我的小侄女一定已经在治疗你了
I'm sure my little niece
is healing you up as we speak.
她来这里做什么？
What the hell
is she doing here?
- 我想帮忙
- 帮忙？
-I'm trying to help.
-Help?
你正是让我们陷入这一切的罪魁祸首
You're the reason
we're in this bloody mess.
为什么我们还没
跟这女巫解除连结呢，以利亚？
Why aren't we unlinked with
this witch already, Elijah?
蕾贝卡，让她试试
Rebekah, let her do what she can.
我或许有种方法能退烧
I may know a way
to slow the fever down,
但我需要一些特殊的草药
but I'm gonna need
some special herbs.
我会用简讯传个清单给你
I'll text you a list.
好吧，很乐意为你们跑腿
Fine.
Happy to play the fetch girl.
这不是凯蒂的店吗？
Isn't this Katie's shop?
她在遗嘱里把钥匙留给了你
She leave you the keys in her will,
还是今天是自助购物日呢？
or maybe it's just
help yourself Tuesday?
你来这做什么？
What are you doing here?
我听说如果将艾草与鼠尾草混合在一起
You know, I read that
if you mix mugwort with sage,
就能得到一种强力的驱吸血鬼药
you've got quite
the vampire repellant,
就算对最顽固的那种也有效
wards off even
the most resilient pest.
你又为什么来这里？
Why are you here?
保护我的城市免受小偷和流氓的破坏
Just keeping my city safe
from thieves and vandals,
但每当我稍微松懈时
总有一个真祖
but every time I turn around,
I catch an Original
被我抓个正着
with their hand in the cookie jar.
那算你走运了
Well, luckily for you,
your cookies...
我对你一点兴趣都没有
...are the last thing
on my mind.
我知道
但我记得
Oh, I can see that.
Though I remember
以前似乎并不是这样
a time when things were different.
或许有那么一次
但不会再发生了
Maybe once.
Not anymore.
樟脑，找到了
Camphor.
Found it.
（下九区夏博内街3631号）
要出去吗？
Going somewhere?
你来早了
You're early.
还好我来得早
Well, it's a good thing I am.
看起来你正准备独自一人
You seem hell-bent
on enacting vengeance
去实施你的复仇大计
all on your lonesome.
问题是，在你送爱格妮丝
The trouble is,
I need something
去见上帝之前
from Agnes before you send her off
我要从她手上拿点东西
to meet her maker.
我提议我们来做个交易
So, I propose we strike a deal.
把她带来
Bring her here.
作为交换，我会保证
In exchange,
I'll even ensure your niece...
你的侄女卡蜜的安全
...Cami, remains safe.
我真不愿将她
I would so hate for her
卷进这一切
to get caught up in all this.
太过分了
我犯了什么罪？
This is outrageous.
What's the charge?
别装了，爱格妮丝
Please, Agnes.
你知道马赛尔统治着这个城市的吸血鬼
You know that Marcel runs
the vampires in this town.
你觉得是谁在控制其他的一切呢？
Who do you think
runs everything else?
我想这就是你要找的东西
I believe this is what
you're looking for.
你好，爱格妮丝
Hello, Agnes.
你竟然和他做交易？
You made a deal with him?
你竟然狠心对西恩痛下毒手
After what you did to Sean,
即使是与魔鬼做交易
我也要让你受尽折磨
I'd deal with the devil himself
just to see you suffer.
你不能伤害我
You can't hurt me.
所有的女巫都不会放过你的
The entire witch community
will turn against you.
够了！
Enough!
拜托，够了
Please. Enough.
我不在乎你们女巫的权术
I don't care about witch politics.
我也不在乎你们那荒诞的
I don't care about
your ridiculous,
收获祭仪式
little Harvest ritual.
我在乎的是这个小玩意
What I care about is this trinket.
解除诅咒，否则我会让你比死更难受
Undo its curse, or I'll show you
things worse than death.
黑暗魔物可没有解除装置
Dark objects don't come
with an off switch.
诅咒下在苏菲身上
The curse took root in Sophie.
她和你的恶魔之子连结在一起
She's linked to your devil child.
诅咒生效只是时间的问题
It's just a matter of time.
她体温越来越高，我们得马上开始
She's burning up.
We need to do this now.
把她放进水里
Get her in the water.
我不明白午夜游泳会有什么帮助
I don't see how a midnight swim
is supposed to help.
她的体温极高
Her temperature is sky high,
水再加上草药
and the water,
with the help of the herbs,
应该能把体温降下来
should cool us down.
喝下去
Drink this.
你要让她的心跳慢下来
You're gonna have to get
her heart rate down.
那我该怎么做？
And how do you suggest I do that?
抱住她
Hold her.
为自救使心跳变慢以及降低血压
It's a natural human remedy
to slow the heart beating
是人类的本能
and reduce blood pressure.
- 这绝对行不通
- 黛维娜会打破这连结
-This is never gonna work.
-Davina will break that link.
我们只需要一点时间
We just need time.
我不能呼吸了
Oh, I can't breathe.
没事的，深呼吸
Okay.
Take long, deep breaths.
海莉，看着我，深呼吸
Hayley, look at me.
Long, deep breaths.
把注意力集中在我的声音上
Just focus on the
sound of my voice.
你会没事的，你会没事的
You'll be okay.
我感觉到连结被消除了
I just felt it lift.
来，上去吧
Come on. Let's go.
以利亚
Elijah.
一旦你弟弟发现
As soon as your brother finds out
连结被打破了
that the link is broken,
他一定会杀了爱格妮丝
he'll kill Agnes.
我知道你不欠我什么
I know you don't owe me anything,
但求你别让他杀了她
but please don't let him kill her.
以利亚，她是我们
Elijah, she's our only access
与生存所需的力量间唯一的桥梁
to the power we need to survive.
答应我你会阻止他
Promise me that you'll stop him.
是我，你在哪？
It's me.
Where are you?
别伤害她，我马上过去
Don't hurt her.
I'll be there shortly.
我答应你最后一件事
I'll make you one last promise.
我不会让我弟弟杀了爱格妮丝
I won't let my brother kill Agnes.
我知道你只是利用我来拯救你的族人
I know you were just
using me to save your people...
但若再有下次，我会杀了你
...but try it again, I'll kill you.
连结解除了
The unlinking worked.
- 也许现在我们可以计划…
- 现在不行，蕾贝卡
-Maybe now we can make plans--
-Not now, Rebekah.
- 这事能等我回来再谈吗？
- 你回来的时候我就不在了
-Can we discuss this when I return?
-I won't be here when you return.
这听起来像是告别
That sounds like a goodbye.
就是告别
I guess it is.
我来纽奥良只是为了确保你的安全
I only came to New Orleans
to make sure you were safe.
你现在安全了
You are.
我本来以为我能
I thought that I might be able
说服你跟我一起走
to convince you
to come with me, but...
但你却急着投身于
...here you are, rushing off
克劳斯、马赛尔
into whatever Klaus and Marcel
和女巫们的阴谋诡计中
and the witches have cooked up...
我终于明白
...and I finally get it.
你永远不会离开这城市
You'll never leave this city.
你永远不会离开克劳斯
You'll never leave Klaus.
那你就该留下
Then you should stay.
你和克劳斯还有马赛尔间的纠缠
This thing that you
and Klaus and Marcel have,
我不想扯上关系
I want no part of it.
我只想自由自在地生活
I just want to be free.
那就去吧
Well, then go.
你是自由的
You are free.
蕾贝卡
Rebekah.
一晚见面两次
Twice in one night.
我简直是太荣幸了
To what do I owe the pleasure?
也许是我的作风老派
但我认为
Call me old-fashioned,
but I believe
告别还是亲自来的好
farewells are best in person.
你救回了以利亚，现在你们俩
Got Elijah back,
and now you're both
要夹着尾巴逃跑了
gonna tuck tail and run.
聪明啊
Smart girl.
祝你幸福
Have a nice life.
他要留下来，我的离开也并非逃跑
He's staying,
and I'm not running.
我只是在沉船前趁早脱身
I'm disembarking a sinking ship.
我还是孩子时，人们就一直在说
People been saying the city
这城市会没落
has been sinking since I was a boy.
如今依旧欣欣向荣
It ain't going anywhere.
嘿，临别前来喝一杯怎么样？
But, hey, how about one
for the road?
怎么，你想把我灌醉
Why, so you can liquor me up
然后说服我留下来吗？
and convince me to stay?
若非如此，你为什么要来？
Why else did you come here?
我是来说再见的
I came to say goodbye.
那就说吧
Then say it.
终于解脱了
(WHlSPERS) Good riddance.
你是个狠角色，爱格妮丝
You're a piece of work, Agnes...
但你知道吗？
...but guess what?
我也不是好惹的
I'm quite a piece of work myself.
你知道吗，我打算以你的残骸
You know, I contemplated
leaving bits of you
装饰你家族的墓园
artfully arranged
outside your family's tomb.
我想这下总该能杀鸡做猴了
I thought it would leave
a fitting message.
不许伤害我的家人
-(GASPS)
-Don't touch my family.
放开她
ELlJAH: Leave her!
我许下了承诺
I gave my word.
你许下诺言的时机
You tend to give your word
总是如此不合时宜，哥哥
at the most inopportune times, brother.
今天所有人一直照你的指示行动
We've been doing things
your way all day.
来嘛
Come on.
轻轻一扭就能把爱格妮丝送上西天
Just one little snap,
and it's toodle-oo, Agnes.
这是她罪有应得
She deserves it.
尼克劳斯，别轻举妄动
Niklaus, do not make another move.
你想要我的原谅
You have asked for my forgiveness.
我可以原谅你
I will grant you that forgiveness...
但不要让我违背诺言
...but do not make me
break my word.
我高尚的哥哥
My noble brother.
这算是显着的成长吧？
How's that for personal growth, eh?
你还是一如既往地爱扫我的兴
Still, it is just like you
to spoil my fun.
这可不一定
Oh, not necessarily.
我许下的诺言是
You know,
I swore you would not die
你不会死在我弟弟手上
by my brother's hand.
我可没说过
I said nothing...
你不会死在我手上
...of my own.
没人在伤害我的家人后能安然无恙
No one hurts my family and lives.
谁都不能
No one.
我离开这里快一百年了
I've been away from this home
almost 100 years,
你居然让我的房间保留原样，丝毫未变
and you haven't changed
a thing in my bedroom.
我想我也许是为了等你回来
I guess I was holding out
hope that you'd come back to it.
但这里的床应该没有
Although I imagine
it's not quite as comfortable
皇宫饭店来得舒服吧
as those beds at the Palace Royale.
怎么会，这床很舒服
It's plenty comfortable.
我饿了
I'm famished.
我不喜欢吃苹果
Nah.
Apples aren't my thing.
这曾经是你的最爱
They were your favorite
once upon a time.
是的，曾经是
Yeah. They were.
我在种植园干活时
Get my ass beat
if I ever ate them
若敢偷吃苹果会被打个半死
working on that plantation,
即使是腐坏的也不例外
even the spoiled ones.
现在它们只会让我想起
Now they just
remind me of a time
我一无所有的日子
when I couldn't have things.
如今你能获得想要的一切
Well, now you can have
whatever you want.
跟我一起走
Come with me.
跟你去哪，蕾贝卡？
And go where, Rebekah?
去任何我们想去的地方
Wherever we want to.
我们可以共组家庭
We can build a home together.
把克劳斯、这座城市
We can leave behind
Klaus and this city
还有那些孤儿般的吸血鬼都抛诸脑后
and those Orphan Annie vampires.
那些孤儿般的吸血鬼是我的家人
Whoa, those Orphan Annie
vampires are my family,
这座城市是我的家园
and this city is my home.
这也曾是我的家园
我离开了
It was my home, too, once.
I left.
你逃离了，我留下了
You ran. I stayed.
这个帝国因我而兴盛
This empire,
it thrives because of me,
你却想让我弃它而去
and you want me to run.
人不会逃离自己的家
A man does not run from his home.
我比你活得久得多，马赛勒斯
I have lived a lot longer
than you, Marcellus.
我见证过王朝的兴衰
I have seen kings rise and fall.
我只确定一件事
If there is one thing
I know to be true,
那就是不论你的帝国有多庞大
it is that no matter how
big your empire becomes,
若无人与你分享
it is nothing
那些都是虚无
if you have no one
to share it with.
你想要纽奥良
那就拿去
You want New Orleans,
have it.
我不会阻止你
I won't be here to stop you.
他在哪？我找了他一整天了
Where is he?
I've been trying to find him all day.
马赛尔知道尼克劳斯
没有告诉他真实的住处
Marcel knows that Klaus
lied about where he lives.
我可不是他的监护人，小约
I'm not his damn keeper, Josh.
好吧，那就叫他打个电话给我，拜托了
Fine.
Just tell him to call me, please.
好吧
Okay.
想怎样啊，小约？
(GROANS) What the hell, Josh?
你好
Hi, there.
我是马赛尔
I'm Marcel.
我们好像没见过
I don't think we've met.
你来这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
记得我对你的承诺吗？
Do you remember
the promise I made you?
承诺？不记得
Promise? No.
想起来了
Yes.
你答应我你会查出西恩到底怎么了
You promised you'd find out
what happened to Sean.
我信守了承诺
And I kept my word.
你双胞胎哥哥的行为
Your twin brother's behavior
不是他自己的意愿
was not born of natural causes.
一个女巫下咒让他杀那些人
A witch hexed him
to commit those murders
然后自杀
and to kill himself.
我就知道
I knew it.
我就知道他没有疯
I knew he wasn't crazy.
那个女巫是谁？
Who is this witch?
你不用再烦脑这件事了
You needn't trouble yourself over her.
她已经为此血债血偿了
She has already paid for
her actions in blood.
什么？等等，你杀人了？
What? Wait.
You killed somebody?
我确实帮了点忙
Well, I had a hand in the matter, yeah.
原谅我对你的反应有点意外
Forgive me if I'm a little surprised
by your reaction.
那我应该怎么反应？
How the hell am l
supposed to react?
你把我牵扯进一场复仇谋杀中
You just made me culpable
in a revenge murder
而我从未要求过
I never asked for.
我活了数千年
I've been alive for a thousand years,
我向你保证，很多人死于
and, I can assure you,
many people have died
更微不足道的理由
for far less.
再说，你知道真相了，能好过一些了
Besides, now you can find comfort
in the truth.
真相？
你魅惑了我
The truth?
You compel me.
你让我平静地接受了一些
You make me at peace
with something
原本该让我撕心裂肺的事
that should be
tearing me up inside.
虽然不知道怎么做，但我会
I don't know how,
but I will undo
想尽一切办法解除它
whatever the hell it is
you've done to me,
到那个时候
and when I do,
你会后悔见过我
you're gonna wish
you never laid eyes on me.
嘿
Hey.
你去哪了？
Where you been?
你不是还在为我们那晚小争吵生气吧？
Not still mad about our tiff
the other night, are you?
过去的都过去了
Water under the bridge.
如果你还感兴趣的话，卡蜜归你了
Cami is all yours if you're interested.
我觉得我现在
I'm feeling like now
is not the right time
不太适合谈恋爱
for me to pursue a relationship.
时机就是一切，你懂吗？
Life is all about timing,
you know?
说到这个，我稍早去了你的住处
Speaking of,
I swung by your place earlier
想找你喝酒谈心
to commiserate over a drink,
但你刚好不在
but I must've just missed you.
皇宫饭店不太适合我
The Palace Royale didn't suit me.
我几周前就搬走了
I moved on weeks ago.
不，我是说你另一个住处
No.
I mean your other place.
海莉
Hayley.
有意思的落脚处
Interesting location
to put down your roots,
就在我当奴隶的地方
same plantation
where I was a slave.
我想这就是你从不邀请我过去的原因吧
I guess that's why
you never invited me over.
我太失礼了
我会跟以利亚说的
Well, how rude of me.
I'll speak to Elijah.
我相信他今晚一定很乐意
I'm sure he'll be pleased to host
招待你和黛维娜
you and Davina for the evening.
尤其是在你如此热情招待过他之后
Especially after you were
so hospitable to him.
很好
Good.
我很期待
I look forward to it.
再见就是再见，以利亚
Goodbye means goodbye, Elijah.
她和你在一起吗？
Is she with you?
你在说什么？
What the hell are you talking about?
海莉不见了，她在哪？
Hayley is gone.
Where is she?
什么？
What?
马赛尔来过这里了
Marcel was here.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）